Those who chant from the river to the sea are either useful idiots who do not understand what they are saying, or worse, people who wish to wipe the Jewish state from the map.
We will have zero tolerance for those who promote or glorify terrorism or peddle anti-Semitism on our streets.
No matter how many ways you try to smack it up, flip it, rub it down, from the river to the sea is not the new N-word.
I know, I know, I know it's not.
You can't be the oppressor claiming that language about freeing the people you're oppressing is oppressive of you.
Am I right?
Even though they know this to be true, I will reiterate once more that from the river to the sea is not about wiping a Jewish state from the map.
What it is about is freeing Palestinians from Zionist oppressive and apartheid rule.
And if that means that Israel needs to be changed in how it exists, then so be it.
It has nothing to do with harming Jewish people or Israelis for that matter.
But he already know that.
They just need Israel to exist so they can get their money.
And they will continue to put Israelis in harm's way in order to do so.
And what's trippy is how the Israelis who support this don't seem to realize that.
They're playing you.